

- +6681-141-1051
- sudapat.songyod@gmail.com
- Bangkok, Thailand

ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm a freelancer. I have no experienced work in Developer before.

I just quiz my job at Bank last year then I've got a chance to learn some languages programming. I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work.

I like to learn new things for improve myself. Let me show you that I have learned and developed on my own from learning these languages. I hope you give me that chance to show greater things in the future on your Business.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JS
- Bootstrap, Github
- SQL
- Adobe Photoshop, Al

SUDAPAT SONGYOD

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Career Objective

- Seeking a challenging position in a reputed organization where I can learn new skills, expand my knowledge, and leverage my learnings.
- To get an opportunity where I can make the best of my potential and contribute to the organization's growth.
- A highly motivated and hardworking individual looking for a responsible role in a organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ttb, Siriraj, Bangkok | Customer Service Officer

Apr 2022 - Nov 2022

- Helped large volume of customers every day with positive attitude and focus on customer satisfaction.
- Communicated with clients regarding account services, statements, and balances.

WE Fitness | Receptionist

Mar 2019 - Oct 2020

- Maintained confidentiality of information regarding clients and company.
- Resolved customer problems and complaints.
- Compiled information from files and research to satisfy information requests.

EDUCATION

Kasetsart University Kamphaengsaen, 2014-2018

B.B.A. Hotel and Tourism Management

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Able to work under pressure.
- Leadership and can be a good follower.
- · Able to adapt, flexible according to the situation.
- Optimistic.
- Eager to learn and self-development.